Finding Aid of the UW-Milwaukee Office of the Chancellor Records, 1933-2014
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1933-2011, UWM Archival Collection 46; 220.4 cubic ft. (224 boxes) 2 film reels 718 digital files (539 MB)
  - 3. Horton Administration Records, 1973-1986
    - Office of International Studies and Programs, 1981-1983 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Office of the Registrar, 1981-1984 (Box 93, Folder 3-4)
    - Office of Women's Studies, 1979-1984 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - One Hundredth Anniversary, Proclamations, 1985 (Box 142)
    - Open Meeting Law, 1973-1979 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Operation Wednesday, 1975-1981 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Oral History Project, 1981-1982 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Organizational Charts, 1967-1981 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Outreach Planning, 1978-1981 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Overhead Generation, 1974-1980 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Overload Payments, 1974-1981 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Parents' and Friends' Association, 1976-1980 (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Parking, 1978-1980 (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Parking and Transit Subcommittee, 1977-1982 (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - Parking and Transit, UPARK, Blue Hole Project, 1973-1979 (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - Part-Time Student Costs, 1978-1981 (Box 93, Folder 17)
    - Part-Time Students, 1977-1980 (Box 93, Folder 18)
    - People's Theater, 1976-1981 (Box 93, Folder 19)
    - Physical Environment Committee, Year 2000 Master Plan, 1981-1982 (Box 93, Folder 20)
    - Physical Plant, 1975-1979 (Box 93, Folder 21)
    - Planning Commission, 1979-1981 (Box 93, Folder 22-23)
    - Polish-American Studies, 1977-1981 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Proposal for Master of Computer Science, 1979-1980 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Psychology Facility Project Planning Subcommittee, 1975-1981 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Public Radio and Television, 1979-1981 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Radio and Television Appearances, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Recording in Classrooms, 1977-1978 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Research at UWM, 1973-1980 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Residual Registration, 1978-1981 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Reuss, Henry S. [U.S. Representative for Wisconsin's 5th Congressional District], 1976-1983 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Riverside Cluster [Local Public Schools], 1974-1975 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Riverside University High School, 1982-1984 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Riverwalk Civic Committee, 1983 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Rosenberg Memorial, 1974-1980 (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - Rotary Club, 1973-1985 (Box 94, Folder 14-15)
    - ROTC, 1982-1985 (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - ROTC Policies Task Force, 1983 (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - Rules and Regulations, 1975 (Box 94, Folder 18)
    - Russian and East European Studies Committee, 1974-1981 (Box 94, Folder 19)
    - Salary Equity Analysis, 1976-1983 (Box 94, Folder 20-21)
    - Sandburg Food Service, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 22)
    - Sandburg Residence Halls, 1975-1985 (Box 94, Folder 23-24)
    - Sandburg Residence Halls, Visitation Hours, 1972-1975 (Box 94, Folder 25)
    - Saturday Classes, 1980 (Box 94, Folder 26)
    - Save A Kilowatt Corporation, 1975-1980 (Box 94, Folder 27-28)
    - School of Allied Health Professions, 1981-1983 (Box 94, Folder 29-30)
    - School of Allied Health Professions, 1983-1985 (Box 95, Folder 1-2)
    - School of Allied Health Professions, Acting Dean, 1983-1984 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - School of Architecture and Urban Planning, 1979-1986 (Box 95, Folder 4-12)
    - School of Architecture and Urban Planning
      - Doctoral Proposal, 1980 (Box 95, Folder 13)
      - PhD in Architecture, 1980-1982 (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - School of Business Administration, 1980-1985 (Box 95, Folder 15-23)
    - School of Education, 1980-1986 (Box 96, Folder 1-8)
    - School of Education
      - Dean, Search and Screen Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 96, Folder 9)
      - Drug Clinic, 1970 (Box 96, Folder 10)
      - Interdisciplinary Programs, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 11)
      - Office of the Dean, 1978-1984 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - School of Fine Arts, 1980-1985 (Box 96, Folder 13-17)
    - School of Fine Arts
      - Dean Search and Screen Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 96, Folder 18)
      - Summer Evenings of Music, 1974-1980 (Box 96, Folder 19)
    - School of Library and Information Science, 1981 (Box 96, Folder 20)
    - School of Library Science, 1978-1981 (Box 97, Folder 1-4)
    - School of Nursing, 1980-1986 (Box 97, Folder 5-11)
    - School of Nursing
      - Doctoral Program in Nursing, Proposal, 1980-1983 (Box 97, Folder 12-13)
      - National League for Nursing Accreditation Report, 1983 (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - School of Social Welfare, 1974-1981 (Box 97, Folder 15-17)
    - School of Social Welfare, 1981-1984 (Box 98, Folder 1-3)
    - School Service Center, 1979-1980 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Science and Technology Museum, 1978-1979 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Secretary of the University, 1977-1984 (Box 98, Folder 6-7)
    - Security Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Seniority Awards, 1981-1984 (Box 98, Folder 9-10)
    - Seniority Lists, 1978 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Sexual Harassment, 1980-1982 (Box 98, Folder 12-14)
    - Sexual Preference, 1978 (Box 98, Folder 15)
    - Sigma XI Scientific Research Society, 1983-1984 (Box 98, Folder 16)
    - Southeastern Wisconsin Regional Planning Commission, 1983 (Box 98, Folder 17)
    - Space Management Planning, 1980-1984 (Box 98, Folder 18)
    - Speeches
      - 1981-1986 (Box 98, Folder 19-24)
      - 1986 (Box 99, Folder 1-5)
    - Sponsored Research, 1980-1981 (Box 99, Folder 6-7)
    - Sponsored Research, Reports, 1980-1982 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - St. Francis Children's Activity and Achievement Center, 1982-1985 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - St. Sava Serbian Church, 1982-1985 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Staff Development Program Report, 1979 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - State Employees Combined Campaign, 1976-1982 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - State Interagency Planning Council, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - Status of Women, 1980-1982 (Box 99, Folder 14-15)
    - Student Advisory Council to the Chancellor, 1980 (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - Student Affairs, 1981-1984 (Box 99, Folder 17-23)
    - Student Affairs, 1985-1986 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Student Association, 1978-1984 (Box 100, Folder 2-6)
    - Student Employment, 1979-1982 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Student Evaluation of Instruction, 1977-1980 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Student Health Center Advisory Committee, 1975-1981 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Student Housing, Co-Educational, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Student Organizations, 1974-1983 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Student Publications, 1975-1979 (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - Student Retention Task Force, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - Student Rights and Responsibilities, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - Student Service and Special Programs, 1980 (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - Sullivan Professorship, 1976-1980 (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - Surveys and Questionnaires, 1975-1983 (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - Taft Institute, 1974-1983 (Box 100, Folder 18)
    - Task Force on Academic Computing, 1982-1983 (Box 100, Folder 19)
    - Task Force on Enrollment Trends, 1977-1979 (Box 100, Folder 20)
    - Technical University of Wroclaw, Poland, 1980-1981 (Box 100, Folder 21)
    - Telecommunications Task Force, Final Report, 1984 (Box 100, Folder 22)
    - Title IX, 1976-1981 (Box 100, Folder 23-24)
    - Title IX, Self Evaluation, 1976 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Title IX Self Evaluation Task Force, 1976 (Box 101, Folder 2-3)
    - Transfer of Credit, 1974-1980 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Transportation, 1982-1983 (Box 101, Folder 5-6)
    - Tuition Surcharge, 1981-1982 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Twentieth Anniversary, Final Report, 1978 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Twenty-Fifth Anniversary, 1980-1981 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Twenty-fifth Anniversary, Proclamations, 1981 (Box 142)
    - Uhrig Foundation, 1961-1978 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Ukrainian Studies, 1980-1981 (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Undergraduate Teaching Improvement Grant Program, 1981-1985 (Box 101, Folder 12-13)
    - Union Activities Board, 1981-1982 (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - Union Policy Board, 1972-1985 (Box 101, Folder 15-16)
    - United Council of University of Wisconsin Student Governments, 1980-1981 (Box 101, Folder 17)
    - United Farm Workers, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 18)
    - United States, Department of Education, 1980-1985 (Box 101, Folder 19-21)
    - United States, Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1977-1980 (Box 101, Folder 22)
    - Universities Field Staff International, 1918-1982 (Box 101, Folder 23)
    - University Club, 1973-1984 (Box 101, Folder 24)
    - University Committee, 1980-1983 (Box 101, Folder 25-27)
    - University Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - University Development, 1980-1981 (Box 102, Folder 2-3)
    - University of Wisconsin, 1979-1986 (Box 102, Folder 4-5)
    - University of Wisconsin Extension, 1981-1986 (Box 102, Folder 6-10)
    - University of Wisconsin-Oshkosh, 1975-1982 (Box 102, Folder 18)
    - University of Wisconsin Press, 1975-1980 (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - University of Wisconsin System, President [Robert M. O'Neil], 1980-1985 (Box 102, Folder 12-17)
    - University of Wurzburg, 1980-1981 (Box 102, Folder 19)
    - University Police, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 20)
    - University Police Committee, 1978-1982 (Box 102, Folder 21)
    - University Relations, 1980-1981 (Box 102, Folder 22)
    - University Relations, 1981-1986 (Box 103, Folder 1-5)
    - University Relations Committee, 1973-1983 (Box 103, Folder 6-7)
    - University Services, 1979-1982 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Upward Bound Program, 1981 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Urban Extension Advisory Council, 1977-1980 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Urban Grants, 1980-1981 (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - Urban Social Institutions, Doctoral Program, 1979-1983 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - UWM Day at Northridge Shopping Center, 1980-1982 (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - UWM Education Association, 1979-1980 (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - UWM Foundation, 1979-1983 (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - UWM Union, 1978-1982 (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - UWM-UWEX Integration, 1981-1984 (Box 103, Folder 17-18)
    - Vail Institute, 1976-1981 (Box 103, Folder 19)
    - Van Pooling Program, 1980 (Box 103, Folder 20)
    - Veterans Programs and Services, 1979-1982 (Box 103, Folder 21)
    - Vice Chancellor
      - [William L. Walters], 1979-1980 (Box 103, Folder 22)
      - [Norma S. Rees], 1982-1983 (Box 103, Folder 23-24)
      - [Norma S. Rees], 1983-1984 (Box 104, Folder 1-3)
      - Search and Screen Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 104, Folder 4-5)
    - Vilas, William F., Estate, 1974-1983 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Volunteer Services Unlimited, 1980-1983 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Wang Word Processing, 1981-1982 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - White, O.C. [Local Radio Personality], 1981 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Winter, Elmer, 1973-1983 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Wisconsin for Research, Incorporated, 1983-1984 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Wisconsin Society for Jewish Learning, 1973-1982 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Wisconsin State Council on Economic Education, 1973-1980 (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Wisconsin, State of
      - Governor, 1973-1983 (Box 104, Folder 14-15)
      - Legislative Audit Bureau, 1984-1985 (Box 104, Folder 16)
      - Legislative Audit Bureau, Reports, 1978-1983 (Box 104, Folder 17)
      - State Building Commission, 1984-1985 (Box 104, Folder 18-19)
    - WUWM Radio Station, 1982-1986 (Box 104, Folder 20-22)
  - 4. Smith Administration Records, 1977-1992
    - Academic Computing, 1984-1989 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Academic Computing Proposal, 1988 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Academic Deans' Council, 1986-1989 (Box 105, Folder 3-6)
    - Academic Deans' Retreat, 1988 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Academic Misconduct, 1981-1987 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Academic Planning Committee, 1986-1989 (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - Academic Policy Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - Academic Program and Curriculum Committee, 1985-1989 (Box 105, Folder 11-12)
    - Academic Staff, 1977-1985 (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - Academic Staff, 1987-1989 (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - Academic Staff Awards, 1978-1989 (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - Academic Staff Committee, 1986-1989 (Box 105, Folder 16-17)
    - Academic Staff Nominations Committee, 1981-1984 (Box 105, Folder 18)
    - Academic Staff Personnel Policies and Procedures, 1981-1988 (Box 105, Folder 19)
    - Academic Staff Professional Development Program, 1986-1988 (Box 105, Folder 20)
    - Academic Staff Review, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 21)
    - Academic Staff Salaries, 1984-1985 (Box 105, Folder 22)
    - Academic Staff Title and Compensation Plan, 1986-1988 (Box 105, Folder 23)
    - Academic Staff Title and Compensation Study
      - Final Report, 1986 (Box 105, Folder 24)
      - Final Report Appendices, 1986 (Box 105, Folder 25)
    - Academic Staff Title Structure, 1986 (Box 105, Folder 26)
    - Academic Staff Titling, 1987 (Box 105, Folder 27)
    - Accreditation, 1975-1986 (Box 105, Folder 28)
    - Accuracy in Academia, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 29)
    - Ad Hoc Campus Coordinating Committee on Health and Welfare, 1987-1989 (Box 105, Folder 30)
    - Ad Hoc Committee for the Evaluation of the Planning Process, 1983-1985 (Box 105, Folder 31)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Graduate Assistants, 1973-1987 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Ad Hoc Task Force on UWM's Nondiscrimination Policy and the ROTC Program, 1985-1986 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Administrative Affairs, 1983-1989 (Box 106, Folder 3-6)
    - Administrative Computing Services, 1982-1987 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Administrative Staff Meetings, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 8-10)
    - Admissions, 1984-1988 (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - Admissions and Records Policy Committee, 1984-1987 (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - Admissions Standards and Competencies, 1982-1988 (Box 106, Folder 13)
    - Adult Student Alliance, 1983-1987 (Box 106, Folder 14)
    - Advanced Opportunity Program, 1985-1989 (Box 106, Folder 15)
    - Advisory Committee on Alcohol and Other Drug Use, 1986-1989 (Box 106, Folder 16)
    - Advisory Council for the UW System Great Lakes Research Facility, 1976-1986 (Box 106, Folder 17)
    - Advisory Group on Academic Staff and Limited Appointment Compensation and Classification, 1984-1986 (Box 106, Folder 18)
    - Affirmative Action, 1985-1987 (Box 106, Folder 19-20)
    - Affirmative Action Advisory Planning Committee, 1985-1989 (Box 106, Folder 21)
    - Affirmative Action and Equal Opportunity, 1987-1989 (Box 106, Folder 22-24)
    - Alcohol Policies and Programs Advisory Committee, 1985-1987 (Box 106, Folder 25)
    - Alcoholic Beverages, 1985-1988 (Box 106, Folder 26)
    - Allen-Bradley Company, 1980-1986 (Box 106, Folder 27)
    - Alumni Association, 1986-1988 (Box 106, Folder 28)
    - Alumni Association, 1989-1990 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Alumni House, 1973-1982 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Alumni Survey, 1989 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - American Association for Higher Education (AAHE), 1989 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - American Association of University Professors, 1985-1988 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - American Ethnic Studies Coordinating Committee, 1977-1985 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - American Geographical Society Collection, 1979-1989 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Animal Welfare, 1983-1987 (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Annual Minority/Disadvantaged Report, 1987-1988 (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Annual Reports and Planning Documents, 1988-1991 (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Anonymous Mail, 1974-1988 (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - Appellate Tribunal, 1977-1987 (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - Appointing Authority, 1977-1985 (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - Appointments and Titles, 1975-1982 (Box 107, Folder 14)
    - Arab-Israeli Controversy, 1988-1989 (Box 107, Folder 15)
    - Archives Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 107, Folder 16)
    - Art Museum, 1985-1988 (Box 107, Folder 17)
    - Art Museum Policy Committee, 1983-1988 (Box 107, Folder 18)
    - Asbestos on Campus, 1983-1987 (Box 107, Folder 19)
    - Assistant Scientist, 1980-1981 (Box 107, Folder 20)
    - Assistant to the Chancellor, 1984-1987 (Box 107, Folder 21)
    - Association of Women in Education (AWE), 1985-1987 (Box 107, Folder 22)
    - Athletic Board, 1983-1989 (Box 107, Folder 23-24)
    - Athletic Development, 1988 (Box 107, Folder 25)
    - Athletic Facilities, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 26)
    - Athletics, 1987-1989 (Box 107, Folder 27-29)
    - Atmospheric Sciences, 1978-1981 (Box 107, Folder 30)
    - Audit Policy, Credit Classes, 1972-1984 (Box 107, Folder 31)
    - Auditorium/Convocation Center Projects (President's Committee), 1987 (Box 107, Folder 32)
    - Audits
      - External, 1984-1986 (Box 107, Folder 33)
      - Internal, 1985-1989 (Box 108, Folder 1-5)
    - Auxiliary Cash Reserves, 1986-1987 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Awards Ceremony, 1986-1988 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Awards and Recognition Committee, 1980-1988 (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Awards Ceremony, 1986 (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Bachelor's Program in Information Resource Management, 1985-1987 (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Baker Fieldhouse, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - Bequests, 1977-1983 (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - Biennial Working Group on Faculty and Academic Staff Compensation, 1982-1984 (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - Biotechnology, 1986-1987 (Box 108, Folder 13)
    - Black State Employees, 1980-1986 (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - Black Student Union, 1982-1988 (Box 108, Folder 15)
    - Board of Visitors, 1986-1989 (Box 108, Folder 16-18)
    - Boards Orientation, 1982-1983 (Box 108, Folder 19)
    - Bookstore, 1986-1988 (Box 108, Folder 20)
    - Brazil/Universidade Federal Do Ceara, 1980-1981 (Box 108, Folder 21)
    - Budgets and Institutional Research, 1982-1989 (Box 108, Folder 22)
    - Bulletins, 1974-1985 (Box 108, Folder 23)
    - Campus Development Plan, 1984-1985 (Box 108, Folder 24)
    - Campus Facility Advisory Group for Physical Education, Athletics, and Recreation, 1986-1987 (Box 108, Folder 25)
    - Campus Hearing Committee, 1980 (Box 108, Folder 26)
    - Campus Ministries, 1980-1987 (Box 108, Folder 27)
    - Campus Planning Process, 1981-1987 (Box 108, Folder 28)
    - Campus Security Committee, 1984-1988 (Box 108, Folder 29)
    - Cap and Gown Program, 1988 (Box 108, Folder 30)
    - Capital Equipment, 1978-1987 (Box 108, Folder 31)
    - Carlsen Scholarship Committee, 1981-1985 (Box 108, Folder 32)
    - Carroll College, 1973-1982 (Box 108, Folder 33)
    - Catchup Pay, 1984-1989 (Box 108, Folder 34)
    - Centennial Celebration, 1985-1986 (Box 108, Folder 35)
    - Center for Economic Education, 1973-1985 (Box 108, Folder 36)
    - Center for Great Lakes Studies, 1981-1987 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Center for Improvement of Instruction, 1981-1986 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Center for Latin America, 1985-1988 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Center for Twentieth Century Studies, 1979-1986 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Center for Women's Studies, 1985-1986 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Centers of Excellence, 1987-1988 (Box 109, Folder 6-7)
    - Chancellor Emeritus, 1979-1982 (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Chancellor's Budget Advisory Committee, 1986-1989 (Box 109, Folder 9-10)
    - Chancellor, Search and Screen Committee, Final Report, 1991 (Box 138, Folder 11)
    - Chancellor's Staff Meetings, 1985-1989 (Box 109, Folder 11-18)
    - Chapman Foundation, 1984 (Box 109, Folder 19)
    - Chapman Hall, 1974-1986 (Box 109, Folder 20)
    - Chapman Hall Renovation, 1982-1987 (Box 109, Folder 21)
    - Civic Center Campus, 1978-1989 (Box 109, Folder 22)
    - Civic Center Campus Implementation Steering Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 109, Folder 23)
    - Civic Center Task Force, 1987-1988 (Box 109, Folder 24)
    - Civic Design Center, 1987 (Box 109, Folder 25)
    - Classified Employees Advisory Council, 1986 (Box 109, Folder 26)
    - Classified Staff Ad Hoc Task Force, 1981 (Box 109, Folder 27)
    - Classified Staff Exceptional Performance Awards, 1986-1988 (Box 109, Folder 28)
    - Codification Committee, 1981-1986 (Box 109, Folder 29)
    - Coffee with the Chancellor, 1974-1989 (Box 109, Folder 30)
    - College Board, 1984-1987 (Box 109, Folder 31)
    - College of Engineering and Applied Science, 1986-1989 (Box 110, Folder 1-4)
    - College of Engineering and Applied Science, Needs, 1987 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - College of Letters & Science, 1984-1989 (Box 110, Folder 6-7)
    - Commencements, 1983-1986 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Commencements, 1986 May-1988 May (Box 110, Folder 9-13)
    - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (CIC), 1984-1988 (Box 110, Folder 14)
    - Committee to Review the Department of Personnel Services, 1986 (Box 110, Folder 15)
    - Committees, 1978-1988 (Box 110, Folder 16)
    - Community Advisory Council, 1988 (Box 110, Folder 17)
    - Community Organizations, 1984-1986 (Box 110, Folder 18)
    - Comparative Study of Religion Program, 1983-1986 (Box 110, Folder 19)
    - Computer Policy Committee, 1984-1988 (Box 110, Folder 20)
    - Computing Services Division, 1986-1989 (Box 110, Folder 21)
    - Contagious Diseases Advisory Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 110, Folder 22)
    - Continuing Education, 1979-1983 (Box 110, Folder 23)
    - Continuing Fee Income, 1985 (Box 110, Folder 24)
    - Contracting Personnel, 1981-1987 (Box 110, Folder 25)
    - Convocation, 1986-1987 (Box 110, Folder 26-27)
    - Convocation, Annual Awards Ceremony, 1988-1989 (Box 110, Folder 28)
    - Cooperative Educational Service Agency, 1984-1985 (Box 110, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence
      - 1986 August-October (Box 110, Folder 30-32)
      - 1986 November-1988 March (Box 111, Folder 1-17)
      - 1988 April-1989 August (Box 112, Folder 1-17)
      - 1989 September-1991 January (Box 113, Folder 1-18)
      - 1991 February-1992 April (Box 114, Folder 1-15)
      - 1992 May-December (Box 115, Folder 1-8)
      - Community, 1986-1989 (Box 115, Folder 9)
      - Deans and Division Heads, 1987-1989 (Box 115, Folder 10)
      - Faculty, Academic Staff, Classified, 1980-1989 (Box 115, Folder 11)
      - Staff, 1982-1989 (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - Council for Advancement and Support of Education (CASE), 1983-1988 (Box 115, Folder 13)
    - Counseling and Advising Network, 1980-1988 (Box 115, Folder 14)
    - Credit Union, 1974-1984 (Box 115, Folder 15)
    - Criminal Justice, 1979-1987 (Box 115, Folder 16)
    - Cultural Foundations of Education, 1973-1986 (Box 115, Folder 17)
    - Day Care Center, 1977-1986 (Box 115, Folder 18)
    - Deaf Interpreter Training Program, 1987 (Box 115, Folder 19)
    - Dean of Students, 1975-1989 (Box 115, Folder 20)
    - Decompression Plan, 1987 (Box 115, Folder 21)
    - Department Chairs, 1969-1985 (Box 115, Folder 22)
    - Department of Administrative Leadership, 1982-1984 (Box 115, Folder 23)
    - Department of Afro-American Studies, 1980-1989 (Box 115, Folder 24)
    - Department of Alumni Relations, 1981-1983 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Department of Anthropology, 1980-1989 (Box 116, Folder 2-3)
    - Department of Art, 1973-1989 (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Department of Art History, 1984-1988 (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Department of Biological Sciences, 1984-1988 (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - Department of Botany, 1975-1984 (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - Department of Campus and Community Relations, 1984-1986 (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - Department of Chemistry, 1985-1989 (Box 116, Folder 9-10)
    - Department of Classics, 1958-1986 (Box 116, Folder 11)
    - Department of Communication, 1985-1986 (Box 116, Folder 12)
    - Department of Community Education, 1984-1987 (Box 116, Folder 13)
    - Department of Comparative Literature, 1980-1988 (Box 116, Folder 14)
    - Department of Curriculum and Instruction, 1982-1988 (Box 116, Folder 15)
    - Department of Economics, 1980-1989 (Box 116, Folder 16)